See it? "The common field cricket,
a.k.a. Gryllus assimilis"...
...which is Latin for "suck it, you lose."
(Sheldon:)Hang on.
Voilà. "The snowy tree cricket,
a.k.a. Oecanthus fultoni"...
...which is Latin for "I'll suck nothing."
(Sheldon:)Of course, I'm joking, because the Latin
for that is "nihil exsorbibo."
(Howard:)That is not Toby, this is Toby.
(Howard:)Raj, what do you think?
(Raj:)Oh. I really don't care anymore.
[LEONARD SIGHS]
(Leonard:)-God, I had the most horrible night.
-What happened?
(Sheldon:)Obviously another carnal fiasco
with the "shiksi" goddess.
(Howard:)Shiksa. Shiksa.
(Sheldon:)Forgive me.
Yiddish was not spoken in East Texas.
(Sheldon:)And if it was,
it wasn't spoken for long.
(Howard:)Yeah, fine, whatever.
The point is you're wrong, again.
(Sheldon:)We haven't established
that I'm wrong once.
(Howard:)Let's go down
to the Entomology Department...
...and let Professor Crawley tell us
what kind of cricket Toby is.
SHELDON: He's a snowy tree cricket.
And his name is Jiminy.